<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Index on daochook Documentation</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Index on daochook Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://daochook.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuring daochook</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/usage/configurations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/usage/configurations/</guid><description>Once daochook is fully and properly installed, you are ready to begin configurations.
Boot Configuration File Format The boot configuration file holds all of the information needed to launch the game client with daochook injected. It also includes some additional configurations used with daochook internally, such as if you wish to enable/disable certain included patches. Please read the following information carefully to ensure your boot configuration file is written correctly.</description></item><item><title>Creating Addons</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/creating_addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/creating_addons/</guid><description>Failure to follow the directions given here will result in your addon most likely not loading or immediately crashing/erroring. Addons are expected to follow a strict layout / guideline in order to be able to load and function properly! Be sure to read carefully before asking for help.
Creating A New Addon Addons are located within the &amp;lt;Path To daochook&amp;gt;\addons\ directory. Inside of this folder, you will see individual folders for each addon, as well as a libs folder which contains a handful of helper libraries that addons can make use of while running.</description></item><item><title>System Requirements</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/installation/system_requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/installation/system_requirements/</guid><description>daochook Requirements daochook specifically requires the following in order to function:
Microsoft Visual C++ Redist. 2022 - https://aka.ms/vs/17/release/vc_redist.x86.exe Latest Client Requirements Before attempting to use daochook, you should make sure that your system meets the minimum requirements for the official Dark Age of Camelot game client.
Minimum Recommended Pentium 4 2.0 GHz or equivalent Pentium 4 3.0 GHz or equivalent 512 MB RAM 1 GB RAM 3.5 GB free hard drive space 3.</description></item><item><title>Addon Table Information</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/addon_table/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/addon_table/</guid><description>The addon table is predefined within daochook for each addon being loaded. This table contains some additional properties that can be used/accessed by an addon while it&amp;rsquo;s running.
You should NEVER attempt to recreate the addon table or set it to a new value!
This will cause your addon to crash and potentially crash the full client.
addon Table Information The following table is the properties available within the addon table.</description></item><item><title>Install via Git (Recommended)</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_git/</guid><description>If you are unsure of using Git or do not wish to use it, then you can instead follow the instructions for downloading the latest release package manually as a .zip file. See Install via Zip instead.
Currently, the best, and recommended, way to install daochook is by using Git. You can either use Git via the command line or install your personal favorite Git client or shell integration. There is no &amp;lsquo;best&amp;rsquo; client or means of using Git, that is entirely personal choice on which you prefer to use.</description></item><item><title>Running daochook</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/usage/running/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/usage/running/</guid><description>Launching daochook daochook expects a boot configuration file to be passed to its launcher when running, such as:
daochook.exe atom0s.ini When the launcher starts, it will take the given file name and locate it within the boot configuration directory automatically.
The path to the daochook boot configuration directory is: &amp;lt;Path To daochook&amp;gt;\config\boot\
Be sure to read the configurations documentation page for more information on how to configure daochook.</description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/events/</guid><description>Events are one of the main ways addons can be used to interact with the game client. daochook hooks onto multiple game functions and then creates/raises an event internally when one of those functions is invoked. When this happens, the internal addon manager will raise the event in every loaded addon whom has registered one or more callback functions to the event being raised. Addons can register more than one callback to an event if needed.</description></item><item><title>In-Game Commands</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/usage/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/usage/commands/</guid><description>daochook includes several custom commands that are built-in, which you can access by typing into the game chat like a normal slash command.
Commands follow the below syntax for arguments:
Syntax Meaning arg The argument is required and should be entered exactly how it&amp;rsquo;s displayed. &amp;lt;arg&amp;gt; The argument is required, a value should be given. &amp;lt;arg...&amp;gt; The argument is required, one or more values should be given. (arg|arg) The argument is required, one of the displayed values should be given.</description></item><item><title>Install via Zip</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_zip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_zip/</guid><description>It is recommended that you install daochook via a Git client for easy updates. See Install via Git if you are comfortable doing so.
Picking An Installation Folder When picking a folder to install daochook to, it is important that you are NOT breaking the following guidelines.
daochook should NOT be installed into a system protected folder.
This means it should not be put into folders (or folders within) such as:</description></item><item><title>bits</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/bits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/bits/</guid><description>This namespace is currently unused.</description></item><item><title>events</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/events/</guid><description>The events namespace contains functions that are used for working with daochook events.
Functions exposed by this namespace are accessed via the prefix: hook.events.
Functions register Registers a new callback function to the given event.
boolean hook.events.register(event_name, event_alias, callback_func); Parameter Name Type Description event_name string The name of the event to register this callback to. event_alias string The alias for this callback. callback_func function The function to invoke when the event is raised.</description></item><item><title>extensions</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/extensions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/extensions/</guid><description>The extensions namespace is not actually a namespace that is accessible directly. Instead, this namespace is used, internally, to extend the functionality of Lua&amp;rsquo;s base types. (ie. boolean, function, number, string, table, etc.)
table Extensions toliteral Converts the given table of numbers (bytes) to a string literal.
string table.toliteral(table); Parameter Name Type Description table table The table to convert to a string literal. Returns (string) The converted table to a string literal.</description></item><item><title>fs (File System)</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/filesystem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/filesystem/</guid><description>The fs namespace contains functions that are used for working with file system operations. Lua does contain some basic file I/O functionality, but this namespace includes a handful of additional functions that make up for where Lua is lacking.
These file system functions make use of the C++ std::filesystem header. The functions are named the same/similar.
For more information on those functions, please visit: https://en.cppreference.com/w/cpp/filesystem
Functions exposed by this namespace are accessed via the prefix: hook.</description></item><item><title>game</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/namespaces/game/</guid><description>The game namespace contains functions that daochook has either hooked onto, or needed to interact with from within the hook due to either the calling convention being unfriendly with FFI or similar. These are generally wrappers that are just forwarded to Lua, giving addons access to call them.
Functions exposed by this namespace are accessed via the prefix: game.
Functions get_version_mode Returns the internal mode enumeration value that was used to read the games client version information.</description></item></channel></rss>