<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Usage on daochook Documentation</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Usage on daochook Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://daochook.github.io/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuring daochook</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/usage/configurations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/usage/configurations/</guid><description>Once daochook is fully and properly installed, you are ready to begin configurations.
Boot Configuration File Format The boot configuration file holds all of the information needed to launch the game client with daochook injected. It also includes some additional configurations used with daochook internally, such as if you wish to enable/disable certain included patches. Please read the following information carefully to ensure your boot configuration file is written correctly.</description></item><item><title>Running daochook</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/usage/running/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/usage/running/</guid><description>Launching daochook daochook expects a boot configuration file to be passed to its launcher when running, such as:
daochook.exe atom0s.ini When the launcher starts, it will take the given file name and locate it within the boot configuration directory automatically.
The path to the daochook boot configuration directory is: &amp;lt;Path To daochook&amp;gt;\config\boot\
Be sure to read the configurations documentation page for more information on how to configure daochook.</description></item><item><title>In-Game Commands</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/usage/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/usage/commands/</guid><description>daochook includes several custom commands that are built-in, which you can access by typing into the game chat like a normal slash command.
Commands follow the below syntax for arguments:
Syntax Meaning arg The argument is required and should be entered exactly how it&amp;rsquo;s displayed. &amp;lt;arg&amp;gt; The argument is required, a value should be given. &amp;lt;arg...&amp;gt; The argument is required, one or more values should be given. (arg|arg) The argument is required, one of the displayed values should be given.</description></item></channel></rss>