<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developers on daochook Documentation</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/</link><description>Recent content in Developers on daochook Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://daochook.github.io/developers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating Addons</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/creating_addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/creating_addons/</guid><description>Failure to follow the directions given here will result in your addon most likely not loading or immediately crashing/erroring. Addons are expected to follow a strict layout / guideline in order to be able to load and function properly! Be sure to read carefully before asking for help.
Creating A New Addon Addons are located within the &amp;lt;Path To daochook&amp;gt;\addons\ directory. Inside of this folder, you will see individual folders for each addon, as well as a libs folder which contains a handful of helper libraries that addons can make use of while running.</description></item><item><title>Addon Table Information</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/addon_table/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/addon_table/</guid><description>The addon table is predefined within daochook for each addon being loaded. This table contains some additional properties that can be used/accessed by an addon while it&amp;rsquo;s running.
You should NEVER attempt to recreate the addon table or set it to a new value!
This will cause your addon to crash and potentially crash the full client.
addon Table Information The following table is the properties available within the addon table.</description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/developers/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/developers/events/</guid><description>Events are one of the main ways addons can be used to interact with the game client. daochook hooks onto multiple game functions and then creates/raises an event internally when one of those functions is invoked. When this happens, the internal addon manager will raise the event in every loaded addon whom has registered one or more callback functions to the event being raised. Addons can register more than one callback to an event if needed.</description></item></channel></rss>