<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Download &amp; Install on daochook Documentation</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/installation/</link><description>Recent content in Download &amp; Install on daochook Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://daochook.github.io/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>System Requirements</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/installation/system_requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/installation/system_requirements/</guid><description>daochook Requirements daochook specifically requires the following in order to function:
Microsoft Visual C++ Redist. 2022 - https://aka.ms/vs/17/release/vc_redist.x86.exe Latest Client Requirements Before attempting to use daochook, you should make sure that your system meets the minimum requirements for the official Dark Age of Camelot game client.
Minimum Recommended Pentium 4 2.0 GHz or equivalent Pentium 4 3.0 GHz or equivalent 512 MB RAM 1 GB RAM 3.5 GB free hard drive space 3.</description></item><item><title>Install via Git (Recommended)</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_git/</guid><description>If you are unsure of using Git or do not wish to use it, then you can instead follow the instructions for downloading the latest release package manually as a .zip file. See Install via Zip instead.
Currently, the best, and recommended, way to install daochook is by using Git. You can either use Git via the command line or install your personal favorite Git client or shell integration. There is no &amp;lsquo;best&amp;rsquo; client or means of using Git, that is entirely personal choice on which you prefer to use.</description></item><item><title>Install via Zip</title><link>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_zip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://daochook.github.io/installation/install_zip/</guid><description>It is recommended that you install daochook via a Git client for easy updates. See Install via Git if you are comfortable doing so.
Picking An Installation Folder When picking a folder to install daochook to, it is important that you are NOT breaking the following guidelines.
daochook should NOT be installed into a system protected folder.
This means it should not be put into folders (or folders within) such as:</description></item></channel></rss>